A Catalog of Instrumental Music Published Before ca. 1800 in the Alexander Mackay-Smith Collection of the University of Virginia
University of Virginia Library
- THREE QUARTETTOS, For Two Violins, Viola, & Violoncello, with a Thorough Bass Composed by JOSEPH HAYDN, Chapel Master to his Highness, THE PRINCE of ESTERHAZY &c &c Op. XXXIII. Pr. 7s. d6. London. Printed by J. Kerpen, No. 19 Wardour Street, Soho., 1783?; H3479; Four parts, quarto, 282x206 (301x21
  [Hob. III: 41 (Op. 33, no. 5)]
  Vivace Assai 2/4
  Largo Cantabile C|
  Scherzo Allegro 3/4
  Allegretto 6/8
  QUARTETTO II E♭
  [Hob. III: 38 (Op. 33, no. 2)]
  Allo. Modo. Canto C
  Largo Sostenutto 3/4
  QUARTETTO III b
  [Hob. III: 37 (Op. 33, no. 1)]
  Allo Modo C
  Scherzo Allo di molto 3/4
  Quartets, strings, op. 33. Selections; Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809; Kerpen, John; London (England); E♭; G; B; 2/4; 3/4; 6/8; C; C|; Allegretto; Allegro moderato; Allegro moderato canto; Andante; Largo cantabile; Largo sostenuto; Presto; Scherzo allegro; Scherzo allegro di molto; Vivace assai
  Hoboken, v. 1, p. 397.
  BUCEM dates this ca. 1782.
  - Violino Primo
  - Violino Secondo
  - VIOLA
  - BASSO
- Six SONATES pour deux VIOLONS et une BASSE. Composes par GIUSEPPE HAYDN a Vienne Opera IV. Pr. 6s. LONDON. Printed & Sold by R. Bremner opposite Somerset House in the STRAND., 1771; H3795; Three parts, quarto, 241x173 (256x181): VIOLINO PRIMO: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-13. Blank, [14]. VIOLINO SECONDO: Same as VIOLINO PRIMO. BASSO: Same as VIOLINO PRIMO. Figured.
  TRIO I E♭
  [Hob. V:4]
  [Hob. V:20]
  [Hob. V:3]
  [Hob. V:17]
  [by Michael Haydn]
  Trios, violins, violoncello, Hob. V. Selections; Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809; Trios, violins, violoncello. Selections; Haydn, Michael, 1737-1806; Bremner, Robert, d. 1789; Bremner, Robert, d. 1789; London (England); Fugue; Minuet; A; D; E♭; G; 2/4; 3/4; 3/8; 6/8; C; Adagio; Allegro; Allegro moderato; Andante; Fuga allegro; Menuetto; Presto; Tempo di menuetto
  , June 8, 1771.
  See Hoboken, v. 1, p. 478, and v. 3, p. 308.
  Trios V and VI are by Michael Haydn. See
  Hubert Unverricht, Geschichte des Streichtrios ( Tutzing: Hans Schneider, 1968 )
  , p. 71.
  - VIOLINO PRIMO
  - VIOLINO SECONDO
  - BASSO
- Six Sonatas for the HARPSICORD or PIANO FORTE, Composed and Humbly inscribed to the Right Honourable LADY CRAVEN, by George Hickes. London. printed for the Author, by Longman & Broderip No. 26 Cheapside, Music Sellers to the Royal Family. King Sculpt., Between 1776 (publishers began at this address: see Humphries- Smith, p. 216) and ca. 1779 (Edmund Broderip of Wells, one of the subscribers, died in 1779); H5236; Score, oblong quarto, 192x256 (202x273): Title, verso blank. "ADVERTISEMENT" and "List of the SUBSCRIBERS.", [i-ii]. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-27. Blank, [28]. Bound with nos. 18 and 78.
  Allegro moderato C|
  Rondeau Allegro C|
  Moderato C|
  Rondo Allegro 2/4
  Sonatas, harpsichord; Hickes, George, 1642-1715; Longman and Broderip [London, England]; King; Longman and Broderip [London, England]; London (England); Minuet; Rondo; B♭; C; D; E♭; 2/4; 3/4; 3/8; C|; Adagio; Allegro; Allegro moderato; Andante; Larghetto; Largo; Minuetto; Moderato; Presto; Rondeau allegro; Rondo allegro; Tempo di minuetto
  The "Advertisement" refers to "the little Author of these musical Attempts (who has but just entered into his tenth year)..."
- Six SONATAS for two German Flutes, or VIOLINS, and VIOLONCELLO, or a Thoro' Bass for the Harpsichord; Composed by JAMES HOOK Pr. 6/. LONDON Printed for C. and S. THOMPSON No. 75 St. Paul's Church Yard. Where may be had Compos'd by the same Author. [list of works beginning with: "Vauxhall and Marybone Songs in 10 Books" and ending with: "Twelve easy Lessons for the Harpsichord"], ca. 1775; H7385; Three parts, quarto, 267x199 (301x205): TRAVERSA PRIMO: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-13. Blank, [14]. TRAVERSA SECONDO: Same as TRAVERSA PRIMO. BASSO: Same as TRAVERSA PRIMO.
  Rondo Tempo di Minuetto 3/4
  Rondo Allegretto 6/8
  Rondo Allegro Assai 2/4
  Allegro Assai 6/8
  Trio sonatas; Hook, Mr. (James), 1746-1827; Charles & Samuel Thompson; Charles & Samuel Thompson; London (England); Minuet; Rondo; A; C; D; G; 2/4; 3/4; 6/8; C|; Adagio; Allegretto; Allegro; Allegro assai; Allegro moderato; Andante; Andantino; Largo; Rondo allegretto; Rondo allegro assai; Rondo tempo di minuetto
  - TRAVERSA PRIMO
  - TRAVERSA SECONDO
  - BASSO
- A Second Sett of Six SONATAS for two VIOLINS with a Thorough Bass for the HARPSICHORD Composed by Max Humble LONDON Printed by WELCKER in Gerrard Street St. Ann's Soho Where may be had, Sonatas for two Violins and a Bass by the following Authors [list of works beginning with: "Kammel 2 Setts" and ending with: "Smith"], ca. 1770; H7875; Three parts, quarto, 258x190 (298x191): VIOLINO PRIMO: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-13. Blank, [14]. VIOLINO SECONDO: Same as VIOLINO PRIMO. BASSO: Same as VIOLINO PRIMO. Title-page of VIOLINO PRIMO has in MS: "s 7/6d".
  SONATA II E♭
  Andante sempre Piano 3/4
  Poco Andante sempre Piano 3/4
  Andante sempre Pia 3/8
  Trio sonatas, set 2; Humble, Maximilian; Welcker, Peter, d. 1775; Welcker, Peter, d. 1775; Welcker, Peter, d. 1775; London (England); Minuet; A; B♭; E♭; G; 2/4; 3/4; 3/8; 6/8; C; C|; Allegro; Andante; Andante sempre piano; Menuet; Poco andante sempre piano
  - VIOLINO PRIMO
  - VIOLINO SECONDO
  - BASSO
- A fourth Sett of SIX Sonatas for two VIOLINS and a Thorough Bass Compos'd by MAX. HUMBLE Price 7=6 LONDON Printed by LONGMAN and BRODERIP No. 26 Cheapside Where may be had by the same Author his other Sett; likewise Trios by [list of composers beginning with: "Allessandri" and ending with: "Lidel"] N.B. Lately Published 6 Quartettos by Cirri and a second Sett of Harpsichord Concertos by Bach, with the greatest Variety of New Music, and Musical Instruments., ca. 1780; H7879; Three parts, quarto, 256x182 (263x188): VIOLINO PRIMO: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-13. Blank, [14]. VIOLINO SECONDO: Same as VIOLINO PRIMO. BASSO: Title, [1]. Music, pp. 2-11. Blank, [12]. Pages 8-11 (SONATAS V and VI) have heading: "VIOLONCELLO OBLIGATTO". Sonatas I through IV are figured; V and VI are unfigured.
  Amoroso sempre piano 3/4
  Andante Cantabile 2/4
  Menuetto Maiestoso 3/4
  Tempo justo di Menuetto 3/4
  Poco Andante 3/4
  Poco Andante e sempre piano 3/4
  Trio sonatas, set 4; Humble, Maximilian; Longman and Broderip [London, England]; Longman and Broderip [London, England]; London (England); Minuet; A; B♭; E♭; F; G; 2/4; 3/4; C|; Allegro; Amoroso sempre piano; Andante; Andante cantabile; Menuetto; Menuetto maestoso; Poco andante; Poco andante e sempre piano; Tempo di menuetto; Tempo di minuetto; Tempo giusto di menuetto
  - VIOLINO PRIMO
  - VIOLINO SECONDO
  - BASSO
- A FIFTH SETT of TRIOS for Two Violins and a Violoncello Composed by MAX. HUMBLE Pr. s7 = d6. LONDON Printed by WELCKER in Gerrard Street St. Ann's Soho, Where may be had by the same Author [list of works beginning with: "6 Trios 1st. Sett" and ending with: "6 Capital Trios by Pugnani"], ca. 1775; H7880; Three parts, folio, 261x188 (267x199): VIOLINO PRIMO: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-13. Blank, [14]. VIOLINO SECONDO: Same as VIOLINO PRIMO. BASSO: Same as VIOLINO PRIMO.
  Rondeau Menuetto 3/4
  Andante Cantabile 6/8
  Trio sonatas, set 5; Humble, Maximilian; Welcker, Peter, d. 1775; Welcker, Peter, d. 1775; Welcker, Peter, d. 1775; London (England); Minuet; Rondo; A; B♭; C; D; E♭; 2/4; 3/4; 6/8; C|; Allegro; Andante; Andante cantabile; Andantino; Menuetto; Rondeau allegretto; Rondeau allegro; Rondeau menuetto
  Title-page of BASSO is quarto.
  - VIOLINO PRIMO
  - VIOLINO SECONDO
  - BASSO
- A Favorite Set of SONATAS for two Violins Violoncello or a Thorough Bass for the HARPSICORD Humbly Dedicated to the Right Honble. Sir Charles Cocks By MAX HUMBLE OP. VII. Flyn Sc Price 7s. 6d London. Printed for Longman Lukey and Co No: 26 Cheapside. Where may be had by the same Author Six Duets 5s. ALSO Barrettes Quartetts 8s. Kammells Notturnos Violins 7. 6. Campionis eight Trios 7.6 Haydns Trios Do. 6., ca. 1775; H7881; Three parts, quarto, 230x181 (232x184): VIOLINO PRIMO: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-13. Blank, [14]. VIOLINO SECONDO: Same as VIOLINO PRIMO. VIOLONCELLO OBLIGATTO: Same as VIOLINO PRIMO. Pages 4-7 (Sonatas II and III) and 10-13 (Sonatas V and VI) have heading: "BASSO". All are figured.
  Andante Sempre Piano 2/4
  Menuetto Rondo e Andantino 3/4
  Boco Andante 3/4
  Rondo Moderato 6/8
  Menuetto Rondo 3/4
  Andante Sempre Piano 3/4
  Rondo Moderato 2/4
  Trio sonatas, op. 7; Humble, Maximilian; Longman, Lukey & Co.; Longman, Lukey & Co.; London (England); Minuet; Rondo; B♭; C; E♭; F; G; 2/4; 3/4; 6/8; C|; Adagio; Allegro; Andante; Andante cantabile; Andante sempre piano; Poco andante; Menuetto rondo; Menuetto rondo e andantino; Rondo allegro; Rondo moderato; Tempo di menuetto
  - VIOLINO PRIMO
  - VIOLINO SECONDO
  - VIOLONCELLO OBLIGATTO
- XII CONCERTOS In Seven Parts FOR FOUR VIOLINS a TENOR and VIOLONCELLO with a THOROUGH BASS for the HARPSICHORD Composed by John Humphries Opera Seconda. LONDON Printed for John Johnson at the Harp and Crown in Cheapside, of whom may be had [list of works beginning with: "Humphries's 12 Concertos Opera 3d" and ending with: "Ricciotti's 6 Concertos"], ca. 1755; H7922; Seven parts, folio, 253x182 (268x190): Violino Primo del Concertino: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-25. Blank, [26]. Violino Secondo del Concertino: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-23. Blank, [24]. Violoncello del Concertino: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-22. Figured. Violino Primo del Concerto Grosso: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-19. Blank, [20]. Violino Secondo del Concerto Grosso: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-18. At head of CONCERTO XII: "Tromba". Alto Viola: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-15. Blank, [16]. Basso Organo: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-20. The beginning of each work in each part signed: "Humphries".
  Poco Largo C
  Largo C - Allegro 3/4
  Largo C - Allegro [C]
  Largo C - Adagio C
  Lento 12/8
  CONCERTO VII D
  Largo C - Allegro 6/4
  CONCERTO VIII A
  CONCERTO IX c
  CONCERTO X B♭
  Largo C - Allegro 3/8
  CONCERTO XI g
  Largo C - Allegro C
  Adagio staccata C
  Concerti grossi, op. 2; Humphries, John, ca. 1707-ca. 1740; Harp and Crown; Johnson, John, fl. 1754-1770; Johnson, John, fl. 1754-1770; London (England); Gavotte; Jig; Minuet; Sarabande; A; B♭; D; F; G; C; 12/8; 3/4; 3/8; 6/4; C|; Adagio; Adagio staccato; Allegro; Allegro ma non presto; Gavotta; Giga; Largo; Lento; Minuetto; Poco largo; Sarabanda; Vivace
  - Violino Primo del Concertino
  - Violino Secondo del Concertino
  - Violoncello del Concertino
  - Violino Primo del Concerto Grosso
  - Violino Secondo del Concerto Grosso
  - Alto Viola
  - Basso Organo
- XII SONATAS, FOR TWO VIOLINS; WITH A THROUGH BASS FOR THE HARPSICHORD. Composed by J: S: Humphries. Opera Prima. N.B. These Sonatas are proper to be play'd with two German Flutes &c. Likewise where these are Sold may be had great variety of new Concertos, Sonatas, and Solos, for all Instruments in use. London. Printed for, and Sold by I: Walsh, Musick Printer, and Instrument maker to his Majesty, at the Harp and Hoboy, in Catherine Street, in the Strand., ca. 1736; H7925 (SONATA VI: A minor); Three parts, folio, 144x176 (259x189): VIOLINO PRIMO: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-20. VIOLINO SECONDO: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-15. Blank, [16]. BASSO CONTINUO: Same as VIOLINO SECONDO.
  Aria Largo 3/4
  Menuett 3/8
  Gigue 6/8
  SONATA IX E
  SONATA X c
  SONATA XII F
  Trio sonatas, op. 1; Humphries, John, ca. 1707-ca. 1740; Harp and Hoboy; Walsh, John, 1665 or 6-1736; Walsh, John, 1665 or 6-1736; London (England); Aria; Jig; Minuet; Sarabande; A; D; E; E♭; F; G; C; 3/2; 3/4; 3/8; 6/8; Adagio; Allegro; Aria largo; Gigue; Largo; Menuet; Menuett; Minuet; Sarabanda largo
  Smith-Humphries, no. 852.
  It is unclear if J.S. Humphries and John Humphries were the same composer. See
  Owain Edwards, "Humphries, John," The New Grove
  , v. 8, p. 792 and
  William S. Newman, The Sonata in the Baroque Era, 3d ed. (New York: Norton, 1972 ), pp. 317-318.
  - VIOLINO PRIMO
  - VIOLINO SECONDO
  - BASSO CONTINUO
- SIX SONATA'S for two VIOLINS and a VIOLONCELLO with a Thorough Bass for the Harpsichord Compos'd by Joseph Jackson Batchelor in Music Late of St. John's College Oxford. LONDON Printed for the Widow, by THOMPSON & SON in St, Pauls Church Yard of whom may be had Just Publish'd. [list of works beginning with: "A Collection of Songs by Jas: Clark of Durham" and ending with: "Abels Overtures for French Horns in eight Parts"], 1760; J64; Three parts, quarto, 262x192 (276x195): VIOLINO PRIMO: Title, verso blank. Blank, [i]. Music, pp. 1-13. VIOLINO SECONDO: Same as VIOLINO PRIMO. BASSO: Same as VIOLINO PRIMO.
  Andante Affettuoso 6/8
  Minuetto Allegro 3/4
  SONATA II a
  Allo. Andante 2/4
  Minuetto Allegro 3/8
  Andante Amoroso C
  Tambourin Allegro 2/4
  Minuetto Amoroso 3/8
  Trio sonatas; Jackson, Joseph, 18 th cent.; Thompson & Son; Thompson & Son; Jackson, Joseph, Mrs.; London (England); Minuet; B♭; C; D; E; F; A; 2/4; 3/4; 3/8; 6/8; Allegro; Allegro moderato; Allegro andante; Allegro assai; Andante; Andante affettuoso; Andante amoroso; Minuetto amoroso; Minuetto allegro; Tambourin allegro; Tempo di minuetto
  - VIOLINO PRIMO
  - VIOLINO SECONDO
  - BASSO
- Trois TRIOS Pour Violon, Alto et Basse. Dédiés A son ami Kreutzer Par Hyacinthe JADIN ŒUVRE 2e. DE TRIOS. Prix 9tt À PARIS À l'Imprimerie du Conservatoire de Musique; Rue des fossés Montmartre. (Gravé par Mlle. Vératé.), ca. 1799; Deest. J260 has plate no. 68 lacking in this exemplar.; Incomplete set. Two parts, wove paper, 262x197 (281x206): VIOLON: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-13. Blank, [14]. ALTO: Title, [1]. Music, pp. 2-13. Blank, [14]. Title-page of VIOLON stamped in lower right: "Ozi".
  I.er TRIO. Par H. JADIN E♭
  Sicilienne 6/8
  Finale 6/8
  2.me TRIO. Par H. JADIN G
  Finale Allegro 2/4
  3.e TRIO. Par H. JADIN F
  Menuet Andante 3/4
  Trios, strings, op. 2; Jadin, Hyacinthe; Vératé, Mlle.; Conservatoire de Musique [France]; Paris (France); Minuet; Rondo; E♭; F; G; 2/4; 3/4; 6/8; C|; Adagio; Allegro; Allegro moderato; Finale; Finale allegro; Menuet; Menuet andante; Rondeau allegretto; Sicilienne
  Jadin's op. 1, also a string trio, is listed in Cochet's catalogue of 1798 (Devriès-Lesure, v. 2, no. 27). Madame Vératté was active as an engraver ca. 1798 to ca. 1799 (Devriès-Lesure, v. 1, p. 171).
  - VIOLON
  - ALTO
- SIX SONATAS for two GERMAN FLUTES or VIOLINS with a Thorough Bass for the HARPSICORD or VIOLONCELLO COMPOS'D BY SIGR. NICOLO JOMELLI. London. Printed for I. Walsh in Catharine Street in the Strand. Of whom may be had For 2 German Flutes and a Bass. [list of works beginning with: "Carcani's Sonatas" and ending with: "Six Sonatas for 2 Violins and a Bass Compos'd by Fred: Nussen, Op: 2a."], 1753; J600; Three parts, folio, 239x176 (254x183): PRIMO: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-13. Blank, [14]. At lower left corner of first page of music of Sonatas II, III, V (pp. 4, 6, and 10): "Del Sigr. Jomelli". At lower left corner of first page of music of Sonata IV (p. 8): "Del Sigr. St. Martini". SECONDO: Title, verso blank. Blank,. [1]. Music, pp. 2-11. Blank, [12]. At lower left corner of first page of music of Sonatas II, III, V, and VI (pp. 4, 5, 9, and 10): "Del Sigr. Jomelli" (on pp. 9 and 10: "Iomelli"). At lower left corner of first page of music of Sonata IV (p. 7): "del Sigr. S. Martini". BASSO: Title, verso blank. Music, pp. 1-7. Blank, [8]. At lower left corner of first page of music of Sonata I (p. 1): "Del Sigr Carcani". At lower left corner of first page of music of Sonatas II, III, V, and VI (pp. 2, 3, 5, and 6): "Del Sigr. Jomelli". At lower left corner of first page of music of Sonata IV (p. 4): "Del Sigr. St. Martini".
  [by Giuseppe Carcani]
  [by Giovanni Battista Sammartini]
  Trio sonatas, D major; Carcani, sigr., 1703-1779; Trio sonatas; Jommelli, Nicolò, 1714-1774; Trio sonata, G major; Sammartini, Giovanni Battista, 1700 (ca.)-1775; Walsh, John, 1665 or 6-1736; Walsh, John, 1665 or 6-1736; London (England); Minuet; C; D; G; 2/4; 3/4; 3/8; C|; Adagio; Allegro; Allegro assai; Andante; Largo; Minuet; Minuetto
  Smith-Humphries, no. 875.
  , September 13, 1753.
  The collection contains a second copy of this item. For another edition of this publication, see no. 165.
  - PRIMO
  - SECONDO
  - BASSO
- SIX SONATAS for two GERMAN FLUTES or VIOLINS with a Thorough Bass for the HARPSICORD or VIOLONCELLO COMPOS'D BY SIGR. NICOLO JOMELLI. London. Printed for I. Walsh in Catharine Street in the Strand. Of whom may be had For 2 German Flutes and a Bass. [list of works beginning with: "Carcani's Sonatas" and ending with: "Six Sonatas for 2 Violins and a Bass Compos'd by Fred: Nussen, Op: 2a."], 1753; J600; Three parts, folio, 239x176 (254x183)
  This is a copy of 163.
  - PRIMO
  - SECONDO
  - BASSO
- SEI SONATE À Tre con due Flauti Traversieri e Basso DI DIFERENTI AUTORI. FAIT GRAVÉ PAR Mr. CHINZER Prix en blanc 6tt. A PARIS Chez Madame Boivin rüe St. Honoré à la Regle d'Or, Mr. le Clerc rüe du Roule à la Croix d'Or, Mlle. Castagneri rüe des Prouvairs, A LION Mr. De Bretonne rüe Merciere AVEC PRIVILEGE DU ROI. Gravé par Mlle. Vandôme, ca. 1750; B/II, p. 366; Three parts, quarto, 236x177 (245x186): Flauto Primo: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-13. Blank, [14]. Flauto Secondo: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-11. Blank, [12]. Pages 3-6 and 8-11 have heading: "Flauto Sdo.". Basso: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-8.
  Del Sigr. Carcani SONATA I D
  Minuet 2/4 [recte: 3/4]
  Del Sigr. Jomelli SONATA II G
  Del Sigr. Jomelli SONATA III D
  Del Sigr. S. Martini SONATA IV G
  Del Sigr. Jomelli SONATA V C
  Del Sigr. Jomelli SONATA VI D
  Trio sonatas; Jommelli, Nicolò, 1714-1774; Boivin, Mme. (Elisabeth-Catherine Ballard), d. s1776; Castagnery, Mlle. (Marie-Anne), 1722-1782; Croix d'Or; De Brotonne, Étienne, ca. 1707-1757; Le Clerc, Mr.; Le Clerc, Jean-Pantaléon, d. 1759; Règle d'Or; Chinzer, Giuseppe, fl. 1745; Vendôme, Marie-Charlotte; Paris (France); Lyon (France); Minuet; C; D; G; 2/4; 3/4; 3/8; C|; Adagio; Allegro; Allegro assai; Andante; Largo; Minuet; Minuetto
  For another edition of these works, see nos. 163 and 164.
  - Flauto Primo
  - Flauto Secondo
  - Basso
- Six NOTTURNOS for two VIOLINS and a BASS Humbly Dedicated to LADY YOUNG of DELAFORD By her Grateful and most Obedient humble Servant Antonio Kammell Opera VI. Price 1s0=d6. LONDON Printed by Longman and Broderip No. 26 Cheapside Where may be had by the same Author. [list of works beginning with: "6 Trios 1st Sett" and ending with: "6 Quartets by Bach"], ca. 1780; K110; Three parts, quarto, 256x187 (265x194): VIOLINO PRIMO: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-13. Blank, [14]. VIOLINO SECONDO: Same as VIOLINO PRIMO. BASSO: Same as VIOLINO PRIMO. "Longman ... Cheapside" is engraved over Welcker's earlier imprint, still visible in part. At bottom of p. 2 of VIOLINO PRIMO: "Engraved by Straight and Skillern St. Martins Lane".
  NOTTORNO I D
  Maestoso C
  NOTTORNO II B♭
  Gig Allegro 6/8
  NOTTORNO III E♭
  NOTTORNO IV g
  NOTTORNO V G
  NOTTORNO VI E
  Allegretto Grazioso 6/8
  Notturnos, violins (2), continuo, op. 6; Kammel, Antonín, b. 1730; Longman and Broderip [London, England]; Straight & Skillern; Longman and Broderip [London, England]; London (England); Jig; Minuet; B♭; D; E; E♭; G; 2/4; 3/4; 6/8; C; C|; Allegretto grazioso; Allegro molto; Allegro assai; Andante; Gig allegro; Maestoso; Menuetto
  - VIOLINO PRIMO
  - VIOLINO SECONDO
  - BASSO
- SEI TRII, DI VIOLINO E BASSO, COMPOSTI DA ANTONIO KAMMELL; DEDICATI ALLA ILLMA. SIGRA. LADY LUCY MANN. London, Printed by Welcker, Gerrard Street Soho. where may be had by the same Author, 6 Duets for 2 Violins Op. 2, ca. 1770; K78; Three parts, quarto, 273x192 (275x195): VIOLINO PRIMO: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-13. Blank, [14]. VIOLINO SECONDO: Same as VIOLINO PRIMO. BASSO: Same as VIOLINO PRIMO.
  Trio sonatas, op. 1; Kammel, Antonín, b. 1730; Welcker, Peter, d. 1775; Welcker, Peter, d. 1775; Welcker, Peter, d. 1775; London (England); Minuet; A; D; E; E♭; G; 3/4; C; Allegretto; Allegro; Andante; Andantino; Grazioso; Tempo di menuetto
  - VIOLINO PRIMO
  - VIOLINO SECONDO
  - BASSO
- A Second Sett of Six SONATAS for two Violins & a Bass Humbly Dedicated To his Excellency Count Vincent of Waldstein BY Antonio Kammell OPERA TERZA. LONDON Printed by Welcker in Gerrard Street St. St. Ann's Soho, Where may be had by the same Author. [list of works beginning with: "Six Trios Opera Prima" and ending with: "the greatest Variety of new Musick by the most Eminent Masters."], 1769; K91; Three parts, quarto, 259x187 (261x191): VIOINO PRIMO: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-13. Blank, [14]. VIOLINO SECONDO: Same as VIOLINO PRIMO. BASSO: Same as VIOLINO PRIMO.
  Allegretto con espressione C|
  Trio sonatas, op. 3; Kammel, Antonín, b. 1730; Welcker, Peter, d. 1775; Welcker, Peter, d. 1775; Welcker, Peter, d. 1775; London (England); Minuet; A; B♭; C; D; F; G; 2/4; 3/4; 6/8; C|; Adagio; Allegretto con espressione; Allegro; Allegro moderato; Allegretto; Andante grazioso; Larghetto; Menuetto; Tempo di menuetto
  - VIOINO PRIMO
  - VIOLINO SECONDO
  - BASSO
- A Second Sett of Six SONATAS for two Violins & a Bass Humbly Dedicated To his Excellency Count Vincent of Waldstein BY Antonio Kammell OPERA TERZA. Price 1s0=6d. LONDON Printed by Longman and Broderip No. 26 Cheapside and No. 13 Hay Market Where may be had by the same Author. [list of works beginning with: "Six Trios Opera Prima" and ending with: "the greatest Variety of new Musick by the most Eminent Masters."], ca. 1780; K92; Three parts, quarto, 259x187 (261x191): VIOLINO PRIMO: Title, verso blank. "MUSICAL PUBLICATIONS Printed and Sold by Longman & Broderip at the Apollo No. 26, Cheapside & No. 13, Hay market London., [1]. Music, pp. 2-13. Blank, [14]. VIOLINO SECONDO: Title, verso blank. Blank, [1]. Music, pp. 2-13. Blank, [14]. BASSO: Same as VIOLINO SECONDO.
  Trio sonatas, op. 3; Kammel, Antonín, b. 1730; Longman and Broderip [London, England]; Longman and Broderip [London, England]; London (England); Minuet; A; B♭; C; D; F; G; 2/4; 3/4; 6/8; C|; Adagio; Allegretto con espressione; Allegro; Allegro moderato; Allegretto; Andante grazioso; Larghetto; Menuetto; Tempo di menuetto
  A later issue of no. 168, with the imprint superimposed on that of the original.
  - VIOLINO PRIMO
  - VIOLINO SECONDO
  - BASSO
- SIX SONATAS for Two Violins & a Bass COMPOS'D BY The Right Honourable The EARL of KELLY. LONDON Printed by WELCKER in Gerrard Street St. Ann's Soho Where may be had the following Trios [list of works beginning with: "Kammels 6 first Sett" and ending with: "Seifferts"], 1769; E780; Three parts, quarto, 256x181 (263x185): VIOLINO PRIMO: Title, verso blank. Music, pp. 1-9. Blank, [10]. VIOLINO SECONDO: Title, verso blank. Music, pp. 1-7. Blank, [8]. BASSO: Same as VIOLINO SECONDO.
  Andante poco Adagio C
  Andante con espresione 2/4
  Trio sonatas; Kelly, Thomas Alexander Erskine, Earl of, 1732-1781; Welcker, Peter, d. 1775; Welcker, Peter, d. 1775; Welcker, Peter, d. 1775; London (England); Minuet; A; C; E; E♭; F; G; 2/4; 3/4; 3/8; Andante; Andante amoroso; Andante con espressione; Andante poco adagio; Andantino; Largo; Minuetto; Tempo di minuetto
  - VIOLINO PRIMO
  - VIOLINO SECONDO
  - BASSO